Finding Aid for the Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo, 2007
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Harbison masterclass, June 2007, X.; 1 CD-ROM (26 image files in TIFF format)
  - Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra with Robert Franz, conductor, Original file name: BPO.tif (Image-file cd10_19)
  - Composer Roger Reynolds with students, Jane Stanley, Carmel Raz, Jenece Gerber, and Patrick Castillo, Original file name: ROGER REYNOLDS Masterclass-.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-097 (Image-file cd10_20)
  - Composer Roger Reynolds with students, Jane Stanley, Carmel Raz, Jenece Gerber, Patrick Castillo, and S. Anthony Amstutz, Original file name: Roger Reynolds Masterclass.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-096 (Image-file cd10_21)
  - Composer Charles Wuorinen gesturing during seminar, Original file name: Wuorinen ---.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-119 (Image-file cd10_22)
  - Composer Charles Wuorinen gesturing during seminar, Original file name: Wuorinen .tif Converted file name: JIB2007-118 (Image-file cd10_23)
  - Composer Charles Wuorinen sitting at desk during masterclass with June in Buffalo students, Original file name: Wuorinen masterclass-=.tif (Image-file cd10_24)
  - Composer Charles Wuorinen with June in Buffalo students: Jacques Baldasari, Paolo Cavallone, John Aylward, Michael McBride, Daniel Van Hassel, Jeff Silva, and Eliza Brown, Original file name: Wuorinen masterclass.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-128 (Image-file cd10_25)
  - June in Buffalo students attending masterclass by Charles Wuorinen, Original file name: Wuorinen masterclass=.tif (Image-file cd10_26)
- Felder Chasmal, Reynolds The Palace, JIB '07, June 2007, XI.; 1 CD-ROM (18 image files in TIFF format)
  - Nicholas Isherwood performing David Felder's Chasmal, Original file name: -Chashmal.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-036 (Image-file cd11_01)
  - Nicholas Isherwood performing David Felder's Chasmal, Original file name: CHASHMAL Isherwood_front.tif (Image-file cd11_02)
  - Nicholas Isherwood performing David Felder's Chasmal, Original file name: CHASHMAL Isherwood_side---.tif (Image-file cd11_03)
  - Nicholas Isherwood performing David Felder's Chasmal, Original file name: Chashmal- David Felder-Nicolas Isherwood.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-035 (Image-file cd11_04)
  - Nicholas Isherwood performing David Felder's Chasmal, Original file name: Chashmal.tif (Image-file cd11_05)
  - Composer Roger Reynolds at sound console with J.T. Rinker, David Felder, Nicholas Isherwood, and James Stephenson, Original file name: FELDER 001.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-094 (Image-file cd11_06)
  - Composer Roger Reynolds examining score with bass Nicholas Isherwood, with J.T. Rinker visible at right, Original file name: FELDER 002.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-092 (Image-file cd11_07)
  - Composer Roger Reynolds examining score with bass Nicholas Isherwood, with J.T. Rinker visible at right, Original file name: FELDER 003.tif (Image-file cd11_08)
  - Composer Roger Reynolds examining score with bass Nicholas Isherwood, Original file name: FELDER 004.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-091 (Image-file cd11_09)
  - Nicholas Isherwood performing David Felder's Chasmal, Original file name: FELDER 008 chashmal.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-034 (Image-file cd11_10)
  - Nicholas Isherwood performing Roger Reynolds's The Palace, Original file name: Isherwood in THE PALACE by Roger Reynolds.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-031 (Image-file cd11_11)
  - Nicholas Isherwood performing David Felder's Chasmal, Original file name: JIB Felder-Isherwood trees.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-037 (Image-file cd11_12)
  - Nicholas Isherwood performing David Felder's Chasmal, Original file name: JIB Felder-Isherwood trees_.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-038 (Image-file cd11_13)
  - Nicholas Isherwood performing Roger Reynolds's The Palace, Original file name: Nicolas Isherwood in THR PALACE.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-030 (Image-file cd11_14)
  - Nicholas Isherwood performing David Felder's Chasmal, Original file name: Nicolas Isherwood....tif Converted file name: JIB2007-039 (Image-file cd11_15)
  - Composer Roger Reynolds with bass Nicholas Isherwood, Original file name: Roger Reynolds_Nicolas Isherwood.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-093 (Image-file cd11_16)
  - Nicholas Isherwood performing Roger Reynolds's The Palace, Original file name: THE PALACE by Roger Reynolds.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-033 (Image-file cd11_17)
  - Nicholas Isherwood performing Roger Reynolds's The Palace, Original file name: THE PALACE JIB 07.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-032 (Image-file cd11_18)
Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the Library's online catalog.
Subjects
June in Buffalo (Festival) (Buffalo, N.Y.)--Photographs; Composers--Photographs; Music festivals--New York (State)--Buffalo--Photographs; Musicians--Photographs
Genres
Photographs; Portraits
Associated Material
Related Resources
Related Resources in the Music Library
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2000
Mus. Arc. 18
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2000 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2001
Mus. Arc. 19
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2001 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2002
Mus. Arc. 20
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2002 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2003
Mus. Arc. 21
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2003 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2004
Mus. Arc. 25
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2004 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2005
Mus. Arc. 27
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2005 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2006
Mus. Arc. 29
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2006 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2008
Mus. Arc. 39
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2008 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2009
Mus. Arc. 50
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2009 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2010
Mus. Arc. 55
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2010 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2011
Mus. Arc. 56
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2011 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2012
Mus. Arc. 60
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2012 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2013
Mus. Arc. 66
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2013 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2014
Mus. Arc. 67
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2014 June in Buffalo.
June in Buffalo Photograph Collection
A selection of images from the June in Buffalo festivals is available through University at Buffalo Libraries Digital Collections.